{
	"questions": [
		{
			"question": "What data structure does a binary tree degenerate to if it isn't balanced properly?",
			"answer1": "linked list",
			"answer2": "queue",
			"answer3": "set",
			"answer4": "OrderedDict",
			"correct": "linked list"
		},
		{
			"question": "What built-in list method would you use to remove items from a list?",
			"answer1": ".delete() method",
			"answer2": "pop(my_list)",
			"answer3": "del(my_list)",
			"answer4": ".pop() method",
			"correct": ".pop() method"
		},
		{
			"question": "What built-in Python data type is commonly used to represent a stack?",
			"answer1": "set",
			"answer2": "list",
			"answer3": "None",
			"answer4": "dictionary",
			"correct": "list"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the term used to describe items that may be passed into a function?",
			"answer1": "arguments",
			"answer2": "paradigms",
			"answer3": "attributes",
			"answer4": "decorators",
			"correct": "arguments"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which collection type is used to associate values with unique keys?",
			"answer1": "slot",
			"answer2": "dictionary",
			"answer3": "queue",
			"answer4": "sorted list",
			"correct": "dictionary"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the algorithmic paradigm of quick sort?",
			"answer1": "dynamic programming",
			"answer2": "divide and conquer",
			"answer3": "decrease and conquer",
			"answer4": "backtracking",
			"correct": "divide and conquer"
		},
		{
			"question": "What symbol(s) do you use to assess equality between two elements?",
			"answer1": "&&",
			"answer2": "=",
			"answer3": "==",
			"answer4": "||",
			"correct": "=="
		},
		{
			"question": "What value would be returned by this check for equality? 5 != 6",
			"answer1": "yes",
			"answer2": "False",
			"answer3": "True",
			"answer4": "None",
			"correct": "True"
		},
		{
			"question": "What does a generator return?",
			"answer1": "None",
			"answer2": "An iterable object",
			"answer3": "A linked list data structure from a non-empty list",
			"answer4": "All the keys of the given dictionary",
			"correct": "An iterable object"
		},
		{
			"question": "What file is imported to use dates in python?",
			"answer1": "datetime",
			"answer2": "dateday",
			"answer3": "daytime",
			"answer4": "timedate",
			"correct": "datetime"
		}
	]
}